upout.com 2016-05-14

# Privacy Policy - UpOut

## UpOut's Privacy Statement

#### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, UpOut collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. UpOut's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how UpOut's visitors use its website. From time to time, UpOut may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. 

#### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to UpOut's websites choose to interact with UpOut in ways that require UpOut to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that UpOut gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an UpOut account to provide a username and email address. In each case, UpOut collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with UpOut. UpOut does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

#### Aggregated Statistics

UpOut may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, UpOut may monitor the most popular posts on UpOut.com. UpOut may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, UpOut does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. 

#### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

UpOut discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on UpOut's behalf or to provide services available at UpOut's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using UpOut's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. UpOut will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, UpOut discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when UpOut believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of UpOut, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an UpOut website and have supplied your email address, UpOut may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with UpOut and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. UpOut takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. 

#### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. UpOut uses cookies to help UpOut identify and track visitors, their usage of UpOut website, and their website access preferences. UpOut visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using UpOut's websites, with the drawback that certain features of UpOut's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

#### Business Transfers

If UpOut, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that UpOut goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror of UpOut may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy. 

#### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by UpOut and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

#### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, UpOut may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in UpOut's sole discretion. UpOut encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. 

#### Changes.

We reserve the right, at its sole discretion, to modify or replace any part of this Agreement. It is your responsibility to check this Agreement periodically for changes. Your continued use of or access to the Website following the posting of any changes to this Agreement constitutes acceptance of those changes. We may also, in the future, offer new services and/or features through the Website (including, the release of new tools and resources). Such new features and/or services shall be subject to the terms and conditions of this Agreement.
